Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) den (Po!) kyuu (Pa!) pikkanko (Hai)
閃いて (Pa!) 輝いて (Pi!) 電 (Po!) 球 (Pa!) ぴっかんこ （はいっ）
Flashing (Pa!) Sparkling (Pi!) light (Po!) bulb (Pa!) That's right (Yes)
shinten shinaiyo
進展しないよ
I can't move ahead,
dare ka jyama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
because someone is hindering me... No, no!
zenzen tarinai sorega mondai no koubaisuu
ぜんぜん足りない　それが問題の公倍数
Nothing that I do is enough, which is an all too common problem.
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I will come to understand it.
naniga hontou no koto... Baby?
何が本当のこと... Baby?
What is the truth of it... Baby?
mitetara kokode zukai shite yo Baby!
見てたらここで図解してよBaby！
If we were to see each other, I would draw you a schematic of it, baby!
kotobamo kazumo kimi wo arasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
I wouldn't show you words or numbers.
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to (kyuuu Paaaaaan!) N no jiryoku de
心がビリビリする  S と（きゅーっ　Paaaaaan!） N の磁力で
Our hearts are flittering about from the
magnetic force of the North and South Poles.
S, S, Super kuttsuite Number I say No.1 boy!
(S, S, Super くっついて Number I say No.1 boy!)
S, S, Super numbers close together. I say No.1 boy!
omedetou!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ima kara kimi wa my, ma, my otakara
いまから君は My, ma, my ゛お-た-か-ら゛
From now on, you're my, my, my "treasure."
tokubetsu nanda dounattemo
特別なんだどうなっても
Just for you, no matter what happens,
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I will hold you tightly, tightly and never let go.
watashi wa koishitai yume ni kenkai wa iranai
私は恋したい　夢に限界はいらない
I want to be in love, and dreams have no need for boundaries, so...
tokubetsu dayone acchattamon
特別だよね　会っちゃったもん
just for me, since we met here by chance...
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
you will forgive me, won't you?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) sei (Po!) kai (Pa!) pittanko (gyuu)
閃いた (Pa!)　輝いた (Pi!) 正　(Po!)　解　(Pa!)　ぴったんこ（ぎゅっ）
It flashed (Pa!) It sparkled (Po!) right (Po!) answer (Pa!) That's right (Embrace)